<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Data Science Portfolio on Vincent DongHoon Lee</title>
    <link>https://Hoooni.github.com/VincentPort/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Data Science Portfolio on Vincent DongHoon Lee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 11:00:59 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://Hoooni.github.com/VincentPort/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2. Web Analytics for Quality Alloys</title>
      <link>https://Hoooni.github.com/VincentPort/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Hoooni.github.com/VincentPort/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>For this first group porject I built a web analytics frame using R to analyze website to improve sales. This case study was from Columbia Business School case works and the team analyze the data using R. R code can be read in Github repository.
 Pain Point : Incapable of developing a website that generates consumer interest, builds customer retention, and furthers brand recognition Findings :  5% average of visitors converts to customers decline to 3% of potential visitors in promo period 38% traffic increase in post-promo period Weight of alloy sold during promo declined by 24.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1. Before you go to DMV for driver&#39;s license</title>
      <link>https://Hoooni.github.com/VincentPort/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Hoooni.github.com/VincentPort/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>For this first porject I built a python text game to check various points using game format. Using a main conceptual framework such as loop, printing, conditional statetment, nested function gamer can get the usefule information before their first visti to DMV.
 Pain Point : Too simple or complicated to make checklist Solution : Make text game to memorize the important things      Link to Github Repository</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://Hoooni.github.com/VincentPort/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Hoooni.github.com/VincentPort/contact/</guid>
      <description>Email : dhtoglobal@gmail.com
Follow me on these social media platform
   Platform URL     Linkedin: https://linkedin.com/in/vincentdhl   Github : https://github.com/Hoooni   Twitter : https://twitter.com/HDongHoon    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>