<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Vincent DongHoon Lee</title>
    <link>https://Hoooni.github.io/VincentPort/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Vincent DongHoon Lee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://Hoooni.github.io/VincentPort/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2. Text Analytics R - Comparison between two presidential candidates</title>
      <link>https://Hoooni.github.io/VincentPort/post/project-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Hoooni.github.io/VincentPort/post/project-3/</guid>
      <description>The report is based on an analysis of Buttigieg&amp;rsquo;s Iowa Caucus speech and Trump&amp;rsquo;s speech using Text analytics technique last spring. Based on the Iowa Caucus rise, if Buttigieg is chosen as the Democratic presidential candidate, there are three things to focus on in a series of primaries and debates with Trump:
First, we should focus more on the brevity and substance of the words we use in our speeches. Second, it is important to exclude overlaps in Trump and the use of the term, and to select and reiterate important key words.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2. Web Analytics for Quality Alloys</title>
      <link>https://Hoooni.github.io/VincentPort/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Hoooni.github.io/VincentPort/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>For this first group project, I built a web analytics frame using R to analyze website to improve sales. This case study was from Columbia Business School case works and I and my team analyzed the data using R. My R code can be read in Github repository.
 Pain Point : Incapable of developing a website that generates consumer interest, builds customer retention, and furthers brand recognition Findings :  5% average of visitors convert to customers decline to 3% of potential visitors in promo period 38% traffic increase in post-promo period Weight of alloy sold during promo declined by 24.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1. Before you go to DMV for driver&#39;s license</title>
      <link>https://Hoooni.github.io/VincentPort/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Hoooni.github.io/VincentPort/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>For this first project I built a python text game to check various points using game format. Using a main conceptual framework such as loop, printing, conditional statetment, nested function gamer can get the useful information before their first visit to DMV.
 Pain Point : Too simple or complicated to make a checklist Solution : Make text game to memorize the important things      Link to Github Repository</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>